Big hero. Bigger responsibility.
Ultraman: Rising is a animation, science fiction,
family film directed by Shannon Tindle.
A star athlete reluctantly returns home to take over his father's duties as Ultraman,
shielding Tokyo from giant monsters as he becomes a legendary hero.
Ken Sato / Ultraman (voice), played by Christopher Sean.
Professor Sato / Ultradad (voice), played by Gedde Watanabe.
Mina / Emiko Sato (voice), played by Tamlyn Tomita.
Dr. Onda (voice), played by Keone Young.
Ami Wakita (voice), played by Julia Harriman.
Game Commentator (voice), played by Rob Fukuzaki.
Ultraman: Rising (Japanese: ウルトラマン: ライジング, Hepburn: Urutoraman: Raijingu) is a 2024
animated superhero film based on Tsuburaya Productions' Ultraman franchise.
A Japanese-American co-production between Netflix Animation Studios and Tsuburaya Productions,
with animation by Industrial Light & Magic, it is the 33rd film in the franchise.
Directed by Shannon Tindle in his feature directorial debut, who also co-wrote
the script with Marc Haimes and co-directed by John Aoshima.
The film stars Christopher Sean as Ken Sato/Ultraman along with the voices of
Gedde Watanabe, Tamlyn Tomita, Keone Young, and Julia Harriman.
Ultraman: Rising was released worldwide on Netflix on June 14, 2024.
The film has received positive reviews from critics, who praised the
animation, writing, and voice performances, particularly Sean as Sato.
The film explores themes of hero, superhero,
villain, family relationships, parenthood.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking.